其實我今天有點遲疑到底要不要提一個計畫
因為覺得這個計畫現在好像不是非常重要
可是還是提一下好了
就是這個計畫是
我忘了是什麼時候
就是我跟Best和Pogo有討論到的一個東西
那我之前幫
不是幫
我之前做過兩個跟GDP有關的藝術展覽
那其實有一些疑問
那所以現在的一個想法就是想要做出一個
台灣文化組織還有個人的關係圖
就是想要知道說政府的錢都補助到哪些機構上
然後這些機構都拿來辦什麼樣的展覽
然後邀請什麼樣的評審
然後邀請什麼樣的藝術家來展覽
就有點像之前Ronnie做過的台灣公司關係圖一樣
就想要知道這些人之間的關係
好
那
I can say this proposal in English myself
I want to do
I want to make a map of all the Taiwanese cultural institutions
and creators and artists and judges and teachers
so that we know how our governments
how or where does our government funding go to
to which institutions and to which exhibitions and to which artists
so we can sort of better understand their relationship
and you know
find out like maybe the isolated parties
or find out like their structure of power
and this project is not that important
so maybe you don't want to talk to me
because we have much more important things to do
than you know talking about art and cultural circles
but if you are interested talk to me
Thanks